<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<newsData>
    <!-- =========================================================================================================== -->
    <news>
        <title>Registration Now Open For NY Capital Hackathon for Inclusivity</title>
        <date>
            <month>March</month>
            <day>2</day>
            <year>2016</year>
        </date>
        <description>
            <paragraph>
                Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute’s inaugural women in tech summit, NYχ,will take place April 16 - 17th
                starting at 9:00am. We hope this event will bring together women in CS throughout the Capital District Region
                while also engaging them intellectually with the conference and a hackathon. You don’t need to be veteran
                hacker to participate! Any woman interested in programming, hackathons, or networking is highly encouraged
                to attend.
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph>
                Who can attend: Do you identify as a woman (cis or trans) or genderqueer? Do you attend school in the
                Capital Region? Do you love (or are interested in) tech? If you answered yes then you are more than
                welcome to attend! All skill levels are encouraged to attend!
            </paragraph>
        </description>
        <links>
            <link>
                <header>Register Here</header>
                <url>https://form.jotform.com/60557575821159</url>
            </link>
            <link>
                <header>Event Schedule</header>
                <url>http://nychi.tech/schedule/</url>
            </link>

        </links>
    </news>
    <!-- =========================================================================================================== -->
    <news>
        <title>Women in Tech Summit Planned For Spring</title>
        <date>
            <month>February</month>
            <day>24</day>
            <year>2016</year>
        </date>
        <description>
            <paragraph>
                The Rensselaer chapter of the Association for Computing Machinery’s Women in Computing (ACM-W) will host
                a one-day “Women in Tech Summit” conference for women in computer science groups throughout the Capital Region.
                The conference is supported through a $5,000 amplification award grant the group recently received from the
                National Center for Women and Information Technology (NCWIT) Student Seed Fund.
            </paragraph>
        </description>
        <links>
            <link>
                <header>Inside Rensselaer Article</header>
                <url>http://www.insiderensselaer.com/women-in-tech-summit/</url>
            </link>
        </links>
    </news>
    <!-- =========================================================================================================== -->
    <news>
        <title>We've Been Awarded a NCWIT Amplification Award!</title>
        <date>
            <month>January</month>
            <day>30</day>
            <year>2016</year>
        </date>
        <description>
            <paragraph>
                ACM-W @ RPI is excited to announce that we have been granted the National Center for Women amd Information
                Technology (NCWIT) Amplification Award sponsored by Google.org! Valued at $5,000 dollars, the Amplification Award was
                created for existing ACM-W chapters seeking to expand their impact though both new and existing opportunities within the campus
                setting and the greater community.
            </paragraph>

            <paragraph>
                With the grant, will be hosting a one-day Women in Tech Summit held on campus that will bring together ACM-W members and other
                women in Computer Science throughout the Capital District Region. This summit will be modeled after the Grace Hopper Celebration
                with emphasis on community creation. The summit will be an exciting place to learn, inspire, innovate and network so we hope to
                see you there!
            </paragraph>

            <paragraph>
                We are grateful to NCWIT and Google.org for graciously funding our summit. Without their financial support it would not be possible
                to create this opportunity. Additionally, we are appreciative for the support provided to us via the Department of Computer Science
                and our advisors Dr. Fran Berman and Dr. Sibel Adali. Their dedication to improving diversity as another means of providing a first
                rate education and academic experience is unrelenting.
            </paragraph>
        </description>
    </news>
    <!-- =========================================================================================================== -->
    <news>
        <title>RPI Chapter of ACMW Featured In XRDS, The ACM Magazine For Students</title>
        <date>
            <month>December</month>
            <day>20</day>
            <year>2015</year>
        </date>
        <description>
            <paragraph>
                This article discusses the ways that our chapter worked to reach out to the community and enhance the role
                of female students in computing.  Former Chair Sarabeth Jaffe details events that our chapter has put on,
                and conferences that our members have attended.
            </paragraph>
        </description>
        <links>
            <link>
                <header>XRDS Article From ACM</header>
                <url>http://xrds.acm.org/article.cfm?aid=2845131</url>
            </link>
        </links>
    </news>
    <!-- ============================================================================================================-->
    <news>
        <title>We've Been Awarded an NCWIT Student Seed Fund Gift!</title>
        <date>
            <month>June</month>
            <day>03</day>
            <year>2015</year>
        </date>
        <description>
            <paragraph>
                ACM-W @ RPI is proud to announce that we have been selected by NCWIT to receive the NCWIT Student Seed Fund gift, sponsored by Symantec.
                This gift is a $1,000 grant which will go towards sending our members to NYCWiC 2016.
            </paragraph>
        </description>
        <links>
            <link>
                <header>RPI's Announcement</header>
                <url>http://news.rpi.edu/content/2015/06/03/association-computing-machinery%E2%80%99s-women-computing-awarded-grant</url>
            </link>
        </links>
    </news>


    <!-- =========================================================================================================== -->

</newsData>