<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>RPI ACM-W</title>
 <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="/"/>
 <updated>2016-01-30T23:37:51-05:00</updated>
 <id></id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Diversity Hack-a-thon</title>
   <link href="/spring%202016/diversity-hackathon.html"/>
   <updated>2016-05-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202016/diversity-hackathon</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>NYCWiC Conference 2016</title>
   <link href="/spring%202016/nycwic-conf-16.html"/>
   <updated>2016-04-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202016/nycwic-conf-16</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Join women from across New York State as we come together for a two day conference for women in tech.
Visit the site for more information: &lt;a href=&quot;http://nycwic.acm.org&quot;&gt;http://nycwic.acm.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Talk from the Global Business Head of Cross-Currency Payments</title>
   <link href="/spring%202016/cross-currency-talk.html"/>
   <updated>2016-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202016/cross-currency-talk</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Morgan McKenney, the Global Business Head of Cross-Currency Payments will be giving a talk. More details comming soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Talk from AthenaHealth</title>
   <link href="/spring%202016/athenahealth.html"/>
   <updated>2016-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202016/athenahealth</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Talk from LinkedIn</title>
   <link href="/spring%202016/linkdin.html"/>
   <updated>2016-02-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202016/linkdin</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How Amazon uses Robots & Algorithms to Deliver Packages to Your Door</title>
   <link href="/fall%202015/amazon-robotics-talk.html"/>
   <updated>2015-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/fall%202015/amazon-robotics-talk</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder how Amazon can process your order, find your item, and get it to your doorstep so quickly?
Come learn about the algorithms and technologies behind Amazon&amp;#39;s fulfillment centers with Amazon Robotics!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon Robotics automates fulfilment center operations using robotic technology including autonomous mobile robots, sophisticated control software, language perception, power management, computer vision, depth sensing, machine learning, object recognition, and semantic understanding of commands.
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazonrobotics.com/#/&quot;&gt;https://www.amazonrobotics.com/#/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food will be provided. For the latest details, check our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/714860261981879/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Elections</title>
   <link href="/fall%202015/elections.html"/>
   <updated>2015-12-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/fall%202015/elections</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ACM-W is holding our annual elections on December 5th at 7pm in Lally 104.
All members should attend and place their vote for next year.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>General Body Meeting</title>
   <link href="/fall%202015/general-body-meeting2.html"/>
   <updated>2015-11-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>/fall%202015/general-body-meeting2</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Join us on November 5th at 7pm in Lally 104 for our second general body meeting of the semester.
We will also be holding an informal tech talk on UNIX Command Line Tools.
Make sure you bring your laptop (please have cygwin installed if you&amp;#39;re using Windows)!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Grace Hopper Review</title>
   <link href="/fall%202015/post-GHC.html"/>
   <updated>2015-10-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/fall%202015/post-GHC</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Join us Tuesday in Union 3510 to discuss our most recent trip to the Grace Hopper Celebration.
This year we sent over twenty members of our ACM-W chapter.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>General Body Meeting</title>
   <link href="/fall%202015/general-body-meeting.html"/>
   <updated>2015-10-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/fall%202015/general-body-meeting</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Our first official general body meeting will be held in conjunction with the weekly Women in CS Cookies and Study/Office Hours/Nerd Talk/Some-of-us knit/crochet/craft/draw meeting held by Professor Cutler and PRofessor Patterson.
Join us Thursday at 7pm in Lally 104.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;d like to join us in the #ILookLikeAnEngineer campaign make sure to be ready to take a picture!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Women In CS Meetup</title>
   <link href="/fall%202015/women-in-cs-meetup.html"/>
   <updated>2015-09-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/fall%202015/women-in-cs-meetup</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Are you considering Computer Science as a major, minor, or dual degree?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you currently studying Computer Science and looking to meet more technical women at RPI?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Develop your network this Tuesday, September 22nd from 8-9pm in Union 3602 at a “Women in CS” meetup!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hosted by ACM-W and the CS Club! There will be fresh baked cookies!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RSVP Here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://sarabethjaffe.typeform.com/to/j7d8v9&quot;&gt;https://sarabethjaffe.typeform.com/to/j7d8v9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>We've Been Awarded an NCWIT Student Seed Fund Gift!</title>
   <link href="/summer%202015/ncwit-student-seed-fund.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/summer%202015/ncwit-student-seed-fund</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to RPI’s ACM-W and all of our supporters!
We’ve been selected by NCWIT to receive the NCWIT Student Seed Fund gift sponsored by Symantec.
This gift is a $1,000 grant which will go towards sending our members to NYCWiC 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&quot;http://news.rpi.edu/content/2015/06/03/association-computing-machinery%E2%80%99s-women-computing-awarded-grant&quot;&gt;RPI&amp;#39;s announcement here&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncwit.org/programs-campaigns/ncwit-awards/ncwit-student-seed-fund&quot;&gt;NCWIT press release here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>We've Been Awarded a NCWIT Amplification Award!</title>
   <link href="/spring%202016/ncwit-amplification-award.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202016/ncwit-amplification-award</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ACM-W @ RPI is excited to announce that we have been granted the National Center for Women &amp;amp; Information Technology (NCWIT) Amplification Award sponsored by Google.org!
Valued at $5,000 dollars, the Amplification Award was created for existing ACM-W chapters seeking to expand their impact though both new and existing opportunities within the campus setting and the greater community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the grant, will be hosting a one-day Women in Tech Summit held on campus that will bring together ACM-W members and other women in Computer Science throughout the Capital District Region.
This summit will be modeled after the Grace Hopper Celebration with emphasis on community creation.
The summit will be an exciting place to learn, inspire, innovate and network so we hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are grateful to NCWIT and Google.org for graciously funding our summit.
Without their financial support it would not be possible to create this opportunity.
Additionally, we are appreciative for the support provided to us via the Department of Computer Science and our advisors Dr. Fran Berman and Dr. Sibel Adali.
Their dedication to improving diversity as another means of providing a first rate education and academic experience is unrelenting.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Valerie Barr (ACM-W president)</title>
   <link href="/spring%202015/valerie-barr.html"/>
   <updated>2015-05-06T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202015/valerie-barr</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Toastmasters</title>
   <link href="/spring%202015/toastmasters.html"/>
   <updated>2015-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202015/toastmasters</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Whether you absolutely love public speaking or want to learn how to wow an audience then you’re going to want to attend ACM-W’s Toastmaster Event on Friday May 1st!
Please RSVP by Thursday, April 30th, at midnight.
Together we will learn to navigate the world of public speaking underneath the guidance of NYISO Toastmasters group will be providing both general instruction and feedback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Closing the tech industry’s gender gap will require more than the stellar technical skills we are improving upon here at RPI.
Having the ability to captivate audiences, sell your ideas, and communicate with others will not only increase your upward career trajectory; but it will also attract other talented women to the field!
The evening will commence with a dessert spread at 6:00pm, followed by the beginning of our program which events at approximately 7:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RSVP &lt;a href=&quot;https://cammiej.typeform.com/to/qoCykI&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.
Please note we are looking for 2 volunteers to do a 4 to 7 minute speech and receive feedback from the NYISO group.
This is an exciting opportunity to get personalized advice on your abilities and areas of improvement.
Additionally, you may amaze the NYISO team who I am told has a wonderful internship program!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Facebook CTO, Mike Schroepfer, vists Data and Society</title>
   <link href="/spring%202015/mike-schroepfer-vist.html"/>
   <updated>2015-04-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202015/mike-schroepfer-vist</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>NYCWic Conference in Syracuse, NY</title>
   <link href="/spring%202015/nycwi-conf.html"/>
   <updated>2015-04-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202015/nycwi-conf</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>GHC Scholarship Grant Application Closes</title>
   <link href="/spring%202015/gdb-scholarship-deadline.html"/>
   <updated>2015-04-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202015/gdb-scholarship-deadline</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;http://anitaborg.org/awards-grants/ghc-scholarship-grants/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Accepted Students Day Activity Fair</title>
   <link href="/spring%202015/accpeted-students-day.html"/>
   <updated>2015-04-11T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202015/accpeted-students-day</id>
   <content type="html"></content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Info Session: Grace Hopper Celebration of Women in Computing Conference</title>
   <link href="/spring%202015/ghc-info.html"/>
   <updated>2015-04-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202015/ghc-info</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Learn more about the Grace Hopper Celebration of Women in Computing Conference.
This year it is happening October 14-16 in Houston, TX.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Informal Chat: Life After Graduate Studies</title>
   <link href="/spring%202015/informal-chat.html"/>
   <updated>2015-03-31T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>/spring%202015/informal-chat</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Join us as we discuss career options after gradate school.
We will be joined by Professor Fran Berman and Professor Stacy Patterson.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
